# Hanna Senkevich

Mobile: +316 85131486 | E-mail: hanna.senkevich@gmail.com | Skype: hanna.senkevich

# **SUMMARY**

Career target: Javascript developer

Work permit: Dutch work and residence permit

Having more that 5 year experience in IT industry in a Business/System analyst role I've gained a good insight of software lifecycle and problem-oriented approach to the customer needs. At my last position I had hands-on experience of web application development. Besides, my university studies gave me solid understanding of main programming concepts.

As a front-end developer, I have a basic skillset and I keep learning new technologies to cover the gaps I currently have. I am highly analytical and I'm focused on delivering solutions that are not only solving user and business problems but are also written in clean and structured code.

#### **CORE KNOWLEDGE & SKILL AREAS**

- JavaScript (ES5, ES6)
- ReactJS
- HTML/CSS
- SCSS/Sass
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Webpack

- NPM
- ESLint
- Git
- Jira
- BDD
- IT Business Analysis
- Agile methodologies (SCRUM, Kanban)

# **RELATED EXPERIENCE**

# Self-education, September 2016 - till now

- Learning front-end technologies at online resources: freeCodeCamp, Coursera, Codecademy, etc.
- Creating web-applications with JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Sass, jQuery.

HiiL Rechtwijzer, The Hague, The Netherlands, February 2015 - April 2017, part time since September 2016 Justice Technology Engineer a.k.a. System Analyst

#### Responsibilities Included:

- System configuration via admin panel UI and Groovy scripting
- Integration with front-end application
- Small fixes of front-end application (HTML, JavaScript)
- Requirements analysis and user story creation
- Development planning
- Jira administration
- Configuration trainings for other team members

<u>Key achievements:</u> 4 platforms designed and successfully implemented within one year.

Reason for leaving this position: decision to change a career direction.

# WARGAMING.NET, Belarus, December 2013 - October 2014 IT Business Analyst at Payment System

# Responsibilities Included:

Requirements gathering and analysis, business processes analysis, designing new features for existing product, designing new systems, API updates, working in close collaboration with development team.

<u>Key achievements:</u> Financial system for transactions reconciliation is designed from scratch.

Reason for leaving this position: relocation to The Netherlands.

# StartupLabs, Belarus, December 2012 - December 2013 IT Business Analyst

# Responsibilities included:

Product concept and vision creation, requirements gathering and analysis, designing new features, creating documentation and BDD scenarios, UI prototyping, managing API integrations, working in close collaboration with development team.

Reason for leaving this position: termination of the company existence.

# Softconveyer, Belarus, November 2010 - December 2012 IT Business analyst /Project Manager

# Responsibilities Included:

Communication with customers, gathering functional requirements, creating prototypes and specifications, <u>projects</u> coordination and delivery.

<u>Key</u> <u>achievements:</u> More than 20 web projects completed for Belarusian and foreign customers (Norway, USA, Australia, Russia)

Reason for leaving this position: looking for new challenges.

# **EDUCATION AND TRAININGS**

**July 2016 – till now** – freeCodeCamp.com, an open source community for learning to code and practicing by building projects for nonprofits.

**September 2012 – December 2012 –** Education Center of Belarusian Hi-Tech Park, Training: Business Analysis in IT

**2011 – 2012** – Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics, Master Course. Master of Economy Science obtained

**2006 – 2011** – Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics. Bachelor of Marketing obtained

# **LANGUAGES**

English Fluent
Dutch Basic
Russian Native
Belarusian Native